The last thing that I want to cover is that you make sure that you get feedback
最后我想说的是 你要确认
from users every step of the way.
在每一个步骤都要从用户得到反馈
Feedback takes a lot of different forms, and you've already seen how
反馈的形式多种多样
you can conduct user research to inform your business idea.
你已经学习了如何进行用户研究得到业务创意的相关信息
You might try incorporating a survey into your product.
你可能要做一个产品调查
You could send these out each week or month to collect feedback, or
你可以每周或每月发送调查收集反馈
you might even try and embed them in some way into your product.
或试着用某种方式将它嵌入你的产品中
Social media is another great way to monitor early usage of your product, and
社会化媒体也是监控产品早期使用的好方法
have customers connect to your brand.
也能让客户与你的品牌联系起来
App ratings, or user ratings, or website ratings, are another way to understand
应用评价、用户评价或网站评价
quantitatively, and qualitatively what users think of your product.
是定量定性地了解用户对你产品的想法的另外一种方式
One app, which is called Circa News provides the following guidance on
有个叫 Circa News 的应用
ratings.
为评价提供了以下指南
First, they recommend that you just build a great product.
首先 他们建议你打造一个伟大的产品
If you don't build a great product,
如果你没有制作出好的产品
users aren't going to give you good ratings in the first place.
用户一开始是不可能给到你很好的评价的
Secondly, don't annoy the users.
第二 不要让用户讨厌你
You should really only ask them to rate your product if they've had a good
你只能够让他们评价他们是否有好的体验
experience and they've used the product for a little bit.
是否有使用产品这种问题
And finally, Circa News recommends that you ask nicely, and
最后 Circa News 建议你温和地询问
maybe even reward your users for rating the app.
甚至给评价了应用的用户给予奖励
For more details about their advice, check out the article,
想知道他们给到的建议的细节 请查看文章
which is linked in the instructor notes.
链接请见讲师注释
Finally, you should make customer support everyone's job.
最后 你应该用客户的意见支持大家的工作
You might have a dedicated email or
你可以分配一个专门的邮箱或者聊天服务
chat service that lets users talk directly to employees.
让用户能够直接与员工对话
Former CCO, and co-founder of Kayak, Paul English, went so
Kayak 的前 CCO 和联合创始人 Paul English
far as putting the very loud phone in the middle of the engineers.
在工程师中间放置了一个声音很大的电话
He reasoned that if the same calls kept coming in,
他说 这是因为如果有用户的电话打进来
then the team would work quickly to resolve the problems.
整组人能够很快地解决这个问题
This would likely resolve the same problems that other users were facing.
这个可能也会同时解决其他用户遇见的相同的问题
No matter which strategy you use, you should think about
无论你使用哪个战略 你都应该考虑
when you'll intercept users and how you will respond to them.
你什么时候询问用户 以及你如何作出响应
Your actions and
你的行动以及对产品的改进
improvements to your product can speak just as loudly as individual follow ups.
与个人跟进有着同等的影响力
But do remember that these experiences also contribute
请记住 这些体验也会影响
to the user's experience and their perception of the product.
用户的体验以及他们对产品的感觉